Are you guys ready?
There are a lot. There are 56
that we're going to be going through.
I think a lot of these are probably
going to be pretty bad, but it's Temu.
So, you know, keep that in mind. Number
one, starting out. And you know, the
weird thing, I'll show you this. The
weird thing about Temu
is everything's always like 85% off.
I Do you think that's like a
seller-based item where they actually
have it on sale, or do you think it's
like a marketing scheme? Cuz there's no
way, like the base price of this product
has to be $4. It's like when Walmart
will like mark stuff down, but it's like
or like Black Friday, I think is a
better example. On Black Friday,
companies will like hike prices up and
then put them percentage Like say a
product costs $100. They're going to
raise the price to 150 and then cut it
by 40% for Black Friday. So, the
product's actually like what, 15% off,
but they're going to market as 40, so
then it appeals to your brain more. Like
this is not This is not a $30 product.
These are like these sheep from that
claymation movie, and I think it's just
a toilet paper holder.
Actually kind of seems fairly useful. I
don't know if this is that good of a
product though. It has one review. Bucks
said, "Super cute. Some assembly
required."
What assembly is required for this? It's
two [\h__\h] items. Do I have to put
together the legs on that? Next.
A fire hydrant.
Well, I don't think it's an actual fire
hydrant. It's a It's a decorative piece,
but I believe it's around like same size
as an actual fire hydrant. How big is
it? Do we get the dimensions?
Really cute, excellent quality,
definitely recommend. Perfect for the
birthday party I used it for. What
birthday party did you use a lifelike or
not a lifelike, a one-to-one fire
hydrant? I love how they just edited it
in different areas. Like that's not
actually there. They just put a PNG of
this fire hydrant there. I guarantee you
it's probably like 8 in tall. Oh, never
mind. It's a foot tall.
Drawn by hand, some differences between
product and pictures. Yeah, that's
[\h__\h] saving their ass because that's
going to come and it's going to be
[\h__\h] shattered in several pieces.
Temu reviews have to be bots. Dude, I've
never seen anything that's a bad review
Oh, "Too small. I thought it would have
been larger." Okay, that's a genuine
review. I always feel like Temu reviews
are always like just [\h__\h] fake. You
know what I mean? Like there's every
product has like five reviews, and
they're all five stars, which is just
crazy. This one seems kind of cool.
I've heard of this. An Aztec death
whistle.
Uh No, yeah, no batteries required. This
is like a wooden a wooden like not a
flute. I mean, it's a whistle. And you
just basically blow really hard into it,
and it just makes a [\h__\h] deafeningly
loud scream or screech. Sound is
awesome, gave us goosebumps. Is it
really that scary? I don't think I've
ever heard one, but I've seen videos
I've seen like fact videos of
uh like how these came to be and how
they would use them. I scared my
neighbors the other night going to get
more.
But he's a menace outside at 1:00 in the
morning just blowing the [\h__\h] death
whistle. No batteries required is one of
the selling points. Bone-chilling
scream. All right, this one seems kind
of cool. Next.
An $18 digital electron microscope.
I don't know what the [\h__\h] I would use
this for. It's showing the CPU. Stable
storage and fast performance. This
device has its own storage func-
functions, so you can take photos and
record them without a memory card. I
just like feasibly can't see this being
anything other than dog [\h__\h] for the
fact that it's 1887.
With $3 shipping. It doesn't even really
seem like a microscope though. Am I
wrong? Cuz in this image here, it's more
like a magnifying glass. Like a
microscope, you're seeing like cells on
a Petri plate. This person just zoomed
in on a penny.
Oh my god, I love this one. It's better
than the first one I got. Each view is
great. The only thing I don't like is
the platform's a bit smaller. The coins
look so sharp when using the microscope.
So, it's for coins. Why is Amy Vincent
obsessed with staring at coins in a
[\h__\h] microscope? I refuse to believe
it has a thousand X
magnifying capability. A thousand times?
That's not what a thousand times on a
coin looks like. Yeah, I need to stare
at my [\h__\h] North Dakota quarter. That
I'm so excited.
All right, why like see and then this
doesn't make any sense. Why is this 76
[\h__\h] dollars? Is this an actual
[\h__\h] stuffed taxidermied possum? What
is this?
Polyester, 13-in possum cuddle toy
plush. $76.03.
I mean, it looks like it's a handmade
high quality. I think it's cuz it's like
an individual seller. He's sold 64, no
reviews.
A smoking pipe.
You guys recommend the dumbest [\h__\h]
Also, I got to say, Floating Candle was
not happy with the amount of dildos and
uh rose toys that were sent as
suggestions. They said it was like 80
80%. I would say like 80% of the
suggestions were were just dildos. All
right, this is just like a 3-ft pipe.
It's for tobacco. I don't smoke tobacco,
and I'm not smoking tobacco. I'll put
weed in it if we have to buy it. I don't
really want to get this.
I feel like this [\h__\h] would not work
well. Seeing how long the pipe is,
you're not getting great air flow. Great
item, thank you. I use it a lot. It
works amazing. Who the [\h__\h] smokes pipes
in 2025?
Excellent item, packaged carefully and
delivered quickly.
Very satisfied satisfied, awesome, good
product. That's a fake person.
A muscle duck.
He holds things. Car keys, jewelry, pen,
and a wristwatch. High quality resin.
Safe material. He's fairly small.
He can only hold one product at a time.
Slightly inefficient. Does he have a
hook? How's he holding that? I think it
might be a magnet. Five out of five,
highly recommend. Affordable and works
great. Can't wait till my duck guards
are tent at Electric Forest. Okay,
that's a real person, but that person is
a [\h__\h] Sims character. Who is
reviewing Temu? I When was Have you guys
ever reviewed a product on any website?
Uh it outside of a bad review. Maybe
like a bad review. I've never [\h__\h]
bought maybe like an expensive item.
Like I could see myself like reviewing
that Iron Man mask because it was $350.
I'm not buying a $7 muscle duck and
saying I highly recommend this product.
It's Is it wooden?
Uh no, it's 3D printed, bro. Uh
That thing's going to [\h__\h] shatter in
the mail.
Grumpy frog statue.
Why are they all different?
Are they all handmade? This one looks a
lot worse than this one.
They're I watched the video.
Oh my god, they got it on a turntable.
Wait, no, I need to see the rest of the
video.
Oh wow, they gave it a butt hole.
I wonder how they make this. This one
looks terrible. I kind of hope I get one
like that. This one like the eyes are
just way [\h__\h] different. Way bigger.
59 reviews. I love this African turtle.
It's so unique and different. I got two,
one for myself and one for my son. We
love them. Made roughly from resin, the
features are amazing. Looks exactly as
advertised. A little expensive. It's $3.
Maybe I'm getting it on sale. Normally
it was eight. It's $3. Expensive.
Honestly, it looks a little rough, haha.
However, I think I like it even more.
These little guys are so cute, they make
you smile. Worth the buy. He probably
got one of the [\h__\h] deformed ones. He
got this one.
No butt hole. Yeah,
imagine one star, no butt hole. Oh, see,
now this is like a a normally priced
product. I don't know how safe Ooh.
Dubai chocolate, one star rating. It's
not good because it's metal. What? Like
they put in metal in the in the snack or
ew, that looks disgusting, actually.
Everybody raves about Dubai chocolate. I
feel like that looks really wet. I
thought Normally Dubai chocolate has
like a flaky crunchy look to it. That
looks like it's like [\h__\h] seaweed.
$22. I feel like out of this review, we
have to eat one fruit food product.
Trending across the web. Carefully
selected premium cocoa or cacao,
emitting a rich and mellow aroma.
Filling blends pure pistachio jam with
crispy breadcrumbs. A luxurious flavor.
Tiara Brown was not a fan. Not a fan.
Vintage cast iron monkey ashtray with
lid. Unique orangutan design. Perfect
for home decor, outdoor use, no
electricity needed.
Can you light this? Oh, no, it's just
literally a remade It's like a cast iron
pan that they remade into a cigar
holder.
I mean, that's kind of cool. I don't
really smoke cigars.
Oh, they have a video.
Oh, somebody Yeah, wow. Non-I love I
love when they play that terrible music
with it. Somebody was just ashing their
cigarette into it. Loving that. It's one
of my favorite things I've gotten from
Temu so far, very sturdy, and the smoke
comes out of his nose. Really cool.
Fun gag gift for my guy best friend.
All his friends call him monkey, and he
smokes so Ooh. And he smokes, so I
thought this was perfect. He He laughed
and absolutely loved the gift. It's
heavier than I expected. Absolutely
adorable ashtray or for trinkets. This
has 120 reviews.
What the [\h__\h] What the [\h__\h]
Conversation piece? So, where'd he get
that? Temu. What is it? It's a monkey
ashtray. End of conversation. That is
not a conversation piece. Where's the
[\h__\h] segue?
A cotton candy machine. I I really think
Dude, I'm so down. Okay, this This says
it's 82% off. Like, that's what I'm
saying. They're not making money if this
is actually normally priced at $165.
That's surely not true. In In modern
times, in American inflation, the
economy's going to [\h__\h] You're tell
You're telling me you're selling me an
82% off cotton candy carnivals uh
[\h__\h] cotton candy machine? You think
it'll break easily? I think it's not
going to come with anything that I need
to make it work. Does it come with the
cotton candy like input [\h__\h] Beautiful,
perfect size for the party.
Ordered flossing sugar when I ordered
this. We already made so much. Okay, so
I have to order the If I order this,
remind If this wins, remind me to order
the [\h__\h] sugar for it. Cuz otherwise,
I'll just have a a cotton candy machine
that's utterly useless.
An off-brand Boston Dynamics robot for
$44.
That is AI. AI intelligent dog. That was
an AI video. That's not a real video.
That's not a real video.
You're You're just showing me a [\h__\h]
fake product right now. It has 89
reviews, so it must work. Robot dog that
can program its own movements. Wow, look
at that complex complex ass controller.
That's how I feel like parents imagine
video game controllers in modern day
looking. Rich app operation functions.
How is this $44? Don't they sell Boston
Dynamics robots for like [\h__\h] 20
grand?
You remember Anybody remember that era
on TikTok where Breck Nurman was
crowdfunding to order a Boston Dynamics
robot dog? And I think he got one for
like 10 grand on Temu. It was like a
really But it was like a higher quality
one. That's a throwback if you remember
that.
Fun toy I have ADHD, struggle to stay
focused, so training it is going to be
difficult. Training it? You have to
[\h__\h] treat it like an actual dog? Oh,
[\h__\h] no. Next one.
A drone. A $10 drone. Comes with two
Needs two batteries or comes with two
batteries. Headlessness mode. When under
headlessness mode, you can ignore the
aircraft's direction. Your forward
You can ignore the aircraft's direction.
Your forward is the direction of the
aircraft. Oh, like relative to where you
are, or it doesn't matter. What's
straight for me is straight for that.
That's cool. 193 reviews. That's
absurdly cheap. This reminds me of those
uh You remember those toy helicopters
from like Toys R Us?
And you'd buy them They would Those
would be like $40. You'd crash them one
time and it would shatter. I I get a
vibe that that's what this is. It works
until you [\h__\h] up one time and then
immediately breaks. So, it full [\h__\h]
pivots on how good of a pilot I am.
Why are his hands dirty?
I can tell you right now this thing
smells bad. Have you ever gone in like
your grandparents' attic? And you get
something or like a storage unit, and
you get something out of a box that
hasn't been touched in like 30 years,
and it has that like weird mildew old
smell? It's going to [\h__\h] It's going to
smell like mothballs. It's going to It's
going to be like a foul scent. Not like
Not like it's like, oh, rotting or
something. It's just going to smell like
dry rot. That is [\h__\h] creepy. I'm
throwing that out if we order that
after. I do not want to keep that in my
vicinity. That is so [\h__\h] creepy.
Okay, this is This is kind of cool.
A USB-powered astronaut crystal ball
night light. This actually looks sick.
Do you get to order the type? Oh, you
get to order the model. So, we would
have to pick which one we want if we get
it. I feel like I'd choose like Saturn.
One of the space ones. I'd make it a
surprise. Ooh, jellyfish is kind of
cool.
This is awesome. I know it's going to be
like cheaply made, but it's also $10.
Cute for any age group that likes the
solar system.
What modern Gen Z kid enjoys the solar
system? Oh my god, there's a video.
Why are they putting some Facebook ass
filter on it? Oh, you can actually take
the light the You can take the ball off.
Oh, you can swap them out. Do I get one
of every type? No.
Oh, it's just show I only get a I get to
order one.
Oh, that looks like a fire hazard.
Next.
I We're buying this. I don't care if
people don't vote for it, I'm buying
this. I think I I've always wanted an
ocarina because I feel like I can play
the [\h__\h] out of this. It's like a cool
ass flute. Oh my god, tell me he plays
it.
>> [music]
>> You think I'm You think I'm ripping it
like that?
I feel like I'm ripping it like that.
>> [music]
>> Oh my god, I feel like I'm ripping it
like that. I full confidence I could do
that.
I would need like one tutorial video.
And I'd blast it.
I'll practice with it before. Has 12
holes. How the [\h__\h] are you supposed to
hold it though?
I can pick color, too. That's kind of
cool. Like Okay, see No, this is what
I'm talking about. $78 originally? $78?
$78? That's what you're charging? That's
what you're charging, Temu. Mm, no. Mm,
no.
Whimsical frog in toilet statue.
Is it just throwing Oh, he's throwing up
from being too drunk. See, if I'm going
to buy a statue, this is the one that I
would rather buy.
77,000
sold. Oh, that's just on their
decorations. I was going to say, no way
they sold 77,000 frogs throwing up in
the toilet.
$17.55.
Not a bad buy.
Next.
One large soft mesh bath brush.
Like you're supposed to scrub your body
with it?
Cleaner and more efficient clean without
dead corners. Bro, this is gross. A bath
brush jumbo super soft.
I bet that shit's like horse hair.
I'm not like I mean, I'll wash my back.
But I'm hitting them with one of these.
I'm getting what I get. I mean, how
dirty is the middle upper part of my
back? Like
I'm not I don't think I need 100% clean
rate on my back. I'm just I'm just going
All right, I don't know if I'm I don't
know if we could buy this.
I I know you guys are going to vote for
it. I can't show this on stream. I Well,
I could show the product on stream, I
can't review it. I can't I can't order I
can't use a flamethrower
inside on a Twitch stream. Like, that's
just And 40 A $42 flamethrower? That
seems like it might explode in my face.
I would film a video outside with it and
then play it on stream cuz I'm assuming
I would have to put this together. And I
got to buy propane. Which would be
annoying. 3,000°?
Kai did it inside?
With a Temu one?
I don't know about a Temu flamethrower.
The best charcoal barbecue wood burning
fire starter I've ever had. Fun and cool
looking. Screw the propane can do it.
Turn on the gas little bit, pull the
trigger, and crank up the gas. Dead easy
to use. Striker works fantastic. Looks
like a toy. Really good at barbecue
bonfire tool. Great for burning weeds.
Really?
I never knew people would purposefully
set their lawn on fire.
If we do it, I would film a video and
then and then show it.
Okay.
Uh a stripper pole.
I think I could set this up. It depends
how how Okay, it's seven It's seven and
nine feet height adjustment wise. Do you
think it would hold my weight? I just
don't want to like break my ceiling.
We all know you could get it. Oh, I feel
like I could swing on this thing, no
problem. I just I if it's going to hold
my [\h__\h] weight. I feel like that [\h__\h]
would detach.
Thick tubing. Static mode and spinning
mode.
How do I like anchor it to my ceiling to
where I wouldn't cuz isn't your ceiling
like drywall to a degree?
It holds 440 lb. No, I know it'll hold
me. I'm just worried if I swing on it,
it'll go ding and [\h__\h] like detach.
I'd be down to get that. I feel like
that'd be fun. Oh.
Sasquatch toes brown bear toes resin
craft. Like why is this a product that
has 57 reviews? Who's buying this? Oh,
it's huge. It's like the size of your
hand.
Highly recommend great bargain gift.
Bro, who the [\h__\h] get If somebody gave
this to me as a gift, I'd be like,
"Dude, you're [\h__\h] terrible." Why
would you I why would I want exactly
it's exactly what I wanted.
Conversation piece. Bro, NPCs.
NPCs are going on Temu and buying weird
products and putting them in their house
so they could have a [\h__\h]
conversation piece. What are you putting
that in your [\h__\h] What is that your
centerpiece in your [\h__\h] table? Oh, I
bet you're wondering why I have a a
wooden Bigfoot toe.
Do you believe in Bigfoot?
Yeah, there's that's the conversation
piece for Michael Patton.
RV has a Bigfoot theme and the toe is
hilarious. This is like the only thing
that makes sense for buying this
product.
You have a Bigfoot theme you're into
Bigfoot. You like Bigfoot. You have a
Bigfoot themed RV.
You have a fake mystery shack. Okay.
Bigfoot toe.
A back scratcher.
Oh, we're scratching a cat with the cat
back scratcher.
I do need a back scratcher. I would love
a back scratcher. This looks like a
really low quality back scratcher. Why
is it $27 cuz it's made of wood?
I love how it's just like a [\h__\h] pain
commercial right now.
I don't think this I don't think this
resembles itchiness. This looks like
somebody's like hurt.
And the cat's supposed to fix it. Study
exactly as described. Dude, have we even
seen a product with one bad review?
Outside of the Dubai chocolate. And it
only had one review.
What is this?
Outdoor and indoor decor for lawn. This
person bought it twice.
It's just like a metal bird.
Product size 6 in by 8 in. $9.
Nine dollars. So many statues
for Temu. You guys recommended a lot Oh.
A taser.
Anti-snatch design this design
specifically designed shock plates on
both sides stunning intruders try to
snatch the weapon away from you.
Like is this TOS if I tase myself?
Anti-grab bar technology. Yeah, well,
what idiot's going to grab the front of
a [\h__\h] taser to take it from you.
You'd probably grab their arm, knock it
out of their hand. Anti-grab technology.
That'd be That would be like you
promoting a knife and with the same
image going, "Anti-grab technology. If
they try to grab the blade of the knife,
they'll get tased." Oh, really?
Perfect for self-defense. The anti-grab
side rails are great idea. 60k volts
will take any attacker down. 60k volts.
I feel like this would give me a heart
attack.
I
I know if I buy this, it's under it's
under the presumption that I will tase
myself when I get it.
Like that is
I I've never I like I don't want to tase
myself. But if I buy it, that's like you
guys are going to be like, "Oh, you got
to tase yourself or you're pussy."
Do a challenge with it? What where I
tase myself? Dude, the reason this looks
so sketchy is it's not a button. It's an
on and off switch. Like it's a [\h__\h] Like
it it's a toy.
Do you see this? Like I'm activating
like a [\h__\h] electric water gun.
Oh my god, this looks so cheaply made.
How to use.
Tasers Teach Teach us would-be attackers
a lesson.
Would-be attackers. They lunge at me,
you just [\h__\h] put them in a coma.
A lightsaber.
The only review says doesn't come with
the connector pieces to make them a
double saber, so it's not a two-in-one.
So you get two lightsabers, but you
don't get the connecting pieces. I don't
even really think that's a bad review
though. Oh, he wanted it so he could
have a double-wielding lightsaber. This
still looks [\h__\h] awesome though. If
this is actually what they're supposed
to look like, $47 almost sold out.
They sell 21,000 products.
Buy two and fight with Brooke.
I'm down to buy that. I mean, dude, it's
whatever you guys vote for.
Uh topical balding scalp solution.
I I know why you guys sent this in.
I'm not that bald. I'm not I'm not
balding. I wouldn't say I'm balding. I'm
not balding nearly to that level. I feel
like if anything, this would make me
start balding. I don't know if I want to
use the Temu topical unscented 1-month
supply East Moon scalp care solution.
Polygonum multiflorum root and ginseng
root extract. Twice a day you're just
supposed to spray it on your head.
Okay, you're kidding me.
This is a random Tik Tok that they
pulled of somebody with good hair. This
woman did not use the [\h__\h] East Moon
scalp care to get that [\h__\h] luscious
hair.
Oh, you're you're [\h__\h] kidding me. Is
the whole Is the whole video just her
hair?
Bro.
That could be a [\h__\h] wig for all I
know.
It has a five-star review.
And that guy bought the item, so.
Musical boxing target. I've seen these
on Tik Tok.
These do look cool. And they go with the
specific beats.
I don't know if you're able to program
songs with them. Probably the more
expensive ones you could program a song.
This one probably pays plays like three
songs.
And they're all non What is this?
I need to hear the audio.
>> [music]
>> Enjoy boxing anytime, anywhere.
All right.
That one does look cool.
Has good reviews too. It has a thousand
reviews.
A full ghillie suit.
They all just play the dumbest music.
I don't think he's blending in very
well. I feel like the color of this
ghillie suit's actually pretty low
quality.
It doesn't have enough shading to make
you feel like you're in a forest. It's
just like a massive green blob moving
around.
Why would you need this? You're
questioning why I would need a ghillie
suit, but you haven't questioned why I
would need any of the other products
we've just looked into.
Oh, this is kind of cool.
It's just a wine glass with a shark in
the middle of it.
That's not really like that fun of a
product, but it is a cool wine glass
nevertheless. I feel like it'll break
after like 10 uses when you put it down
wrong.
A mini archer bow and arrow set.
One archer bow,
a target and a bunch of arrows. 10
suction cups.
Oh, they're suction cup arrows. They're
not actual arrows.
It's a toy.
This would be some [\h__\h] you get at Five
Below. It's $3.59.
I love how it shows you the relative
design next to an iPhone 16. Unique and
well made. Love it, works great. Get the
bigger one, the 9.8 in which I would
have gotten the 9.8 in.
Yes.
I ended up settling for the 7.9 in bow.
It's not really uh as good as the the
9.8. It's kind of hard. It's kind of a
This This one This review would work for
any sex product. Shane Scott. Are we
sure we're reviewing a miniature bow
right now?
A beer hat.
We need to get this.
Shoots cans of all sizes.
If we get this, should I just do a
double beer chug through the [\h__\h]
miniature straw that probably has lead
in it
or [\h__\h] asbestos?
I just start going
with it on top of my head. I feel like
the hat's not going to fit me. It looks
like it doesn't fit around this guy's
head. This worked well for Arizona.
On Arizona iced tea or the state of
Arizona?
Which one?
Oh, this See, okay.
Uh we've had too many statues, but the
statues are getting cooler.
The alien statue hitting me with a shaka
bra holding a beer. You put him on a
ledge. Oh, he can hold a wine glass too.
This is kind of cool.
$7. I feel like only college men own
this.
A foot massager.
Yeah, I know why people want me to order
this one.
Cuz I'd have to [\h__\h] take my shoes
off. I'd be wearing socks on this
[\h__\h] one.
Yeah, no, you're not getting free feet.
Yeah, off off-brand music yet again.
Adapter display.
Are you showing me how it works? Do you
think he'll put his feet in it?
Oh, he's using his hands.
Now, put your feet on it.
No, that's not really showing me how it
works though.
Oh, it has multiple modes.
It has a reverse mode.
This looks incredibly painful.
I don't think I would like this at all.
Who has that What What are your feet
that [\h__\h] sore?
Oh my god, wait. No, this is badass.
Manganese steel sword
traditionally handmade expertise is the
result of long and hard practice.
Detailed super fine 100% love it
recommend awesome strong and durable.
Dude, look how detailed this sword is.
Uh it's probably going to be like that.
Or do you think that's one side and then
there's another side? Cuz that looks
like [\h__\h] in engraved.
Like the whole sword. Oh, the blade's
not engraved. It's the handle.
Dude, that's really cool.
Or sub four stars specifically. Oh, look
how cheap this [\h__\h] spinny hat wheel
wheel thing looks. The kid from Up
wearing this.
This is like a classic dude, this is
like such a known hat in like Hollywood,
I guess. Like you've seen this hat in
movies. I've never seen someone wear
this hat in real life. Like a propeller
spinny hat cuz it's just [\h__\h]
pointless.
I don't think I've ever seen one in real
life.
Smelling salts
Those Temu smelling salts it's ammonia
not poppers.
The [\h__\h] does that mean? Oh, like the
crackable tablets? Yeah, it's probably
just a jar of ammonia. The [\h__\h] did you
think you were getting? Instant death?
Yeah, no, I'd try this. I've tried
ammonia before. That [\h__\h] makes you
[\h__\h] wired.
Cuz it's the [\h__\h] that gets released
into your body when you're dying.
So, it just makes you think you're
dying. That's how they wake people up.
Like you you could be like knocked out
cold if they put ammonia under your
nose, you just
[\h__\h] wake the wake the [\h__\h] up.
Oh my god, wait. The products are
getting better now.
Look at this. I used to see people put
shrimp on these in like the old Tik Tok
days. Somebody put their hand on it.
Does this not electrocute you? Tesla
coil music arc plasma desktop toy
science education set teaching
experiment
How does this not electrocute you?
It doesn't hurt. Oh, it's probably like
a tickle.
It's like a [\h__\h] flashbang, though.
Oh, you could change the strength of it.
It's too small to even project past your
skin. Oh.
He put something on it. What did he put
on it?
He put like light bulbs around it.
Should I get a dead shrimp to put on it?
That's what I always see on Tik Tok.
A weed blanket I have too many blankets,
bro. I know you guys are probably going
to vote for this.
Her username is Cassie Weed. Cassie Weed
Cassie Weed got the weed blanket.
Shocker.
A unicycle
This would be badass to learn how to
ride a unicycle. I don't know if I'd be
able to balance on it but I could maybe
practice before the stream. It's just
full balancing. The seat looks wide
enough for me to sit on. It doesn't
really have reviews. But it's 12% off.
See, that's a reasonable That's a
reasonable markdown. This and the
propeller hat Oh my god, this No, this
the beer hat or the propeller hat and a
taser
Imagine it Imagine me just strolling
down the streets in that. I have a beer
hat on, a [\h__\h] taser and a in one
hand, a flamethrower in the other. Oh my
god, I used to own one of these. Oh my
god, I showed one of these on stream.
These [\h__\h] hurt. These [\h__\h] hurt.
Dude, you hold one of these, you play
hot potato with it. It's just like a
shock ball. I hope it shows somebody
getting shocked. Why are they holding it
with their feet?
The second it zaps you, yeah, you like
can't move.
Yeah, the Sidemen used it, too.
It is a fun little game. It looks like a
Fushigi ball. Where you just try to not
You try to not touch it cuz the second
it shocks you, your hands just go
and then you start holding it. And then
it's just zapping you perpetually.
It's a fun game. I think you could
change the strength on it, too. No
reaction.
I'd rather buy that than the taser. I
don't think I'm allowed to tase myself.
We'll see what chat votes. I get one
veto, so I'll determine what I want to
veto. Next
Mischief Monkey Plush
It's just a toy monkey. Boring. Next a
rubber band shooter This looks 3D
printed.
Uh maybe not. I do love rubber band
shooters, though. I used to own one of
those. I I feel like everybody used to
own a rubber band shooter. I had one
that was like a multi-shot. This is like
a single fire. I used to have one that
had like three gauges and you would
shoot it and you could shoot three at
once. Oh my god, the latter half of this
review, the products are just getting
better. A floating orb
levitating galaxy constellation lamp
Are you [\h__\h] kidding me?
And it shows all the stars in the sky.
This is awesome. That's [\h__\h] sick.
I used to think these were magic. It's
just magnets.
It's just magnets on the ends, so
they're just constantly pushing against
each other. It's not floating.
What is this?
It's a lollipop.
Isomaltitol
amazing tasty sound sweet gift
Is there a speaker in it? What?
Oh, it has a speaker.
Wow.
So, it plays a song as you suck on it.
Oh, do you think it vibrates the song
into your mouth? Listen music through
your mouth. Wait, that's actually so
cool. That reminds me You remember those
toothbrushes that used to sell like way
back they used to advertise them on like
Nickelodeon and they would play songs.
It would be like a toothbrush that has
like three songs auto-cued on Yeah,
tooth tunes. That's a That is a cool
product, though. I wonder what songs it
plays.
A fish mask
Looking very professional here. The
thinker pose He kind of looks fainted
there.
Mhm, interesting. Mhm, he I think he I
think he has a thinking face there. Very
fashionable. Is he drinking hand
sanitizer?
What are we doing there?
Oh, what are What are we doing there?
Is this a grenade?
Oh, no, it's a lighter. Oh my god. I was
just saying they're not selling a
grenade. I hate these. I'm already
saying if you guys vote this, I'm
[\h__\h] No, I'm not I'm vetoing this.
This looks like a deactivated nuke.
A miniature nuclear bomb replica
This is giving like
Fallout 4 vibes. Like the Fallout show.
This is kind of cool. If you had like a
themed room around this. Yeah, Fallout
mini nuke.
The ab workout machine
I remember they used to promote these so
much on early Tik Tok shop. It was like,
"Hey, here's a quick way to get a
six-pack." It just electrically
stimulates your abs. It works in the
sense that it like it makes you flex
your abs. It might give them a slight
workout. I remember I would see That was
a part of the joke, but I would see like
guys that were like very overweight put
these on and be like, "I'm getting a
six-pack." This is not going to help you
lose weight.
But it just jiggles your stomach.
Oh, dude, it has 2,000 reviews. I love
this. Felt my abs felt amazing. Not for
people just starting out. It's powerful
alone. What it is that the side don't
very stick very well, but but tie it
together and prepare for a workout. Or
you just [\h__\h] work out. Like this is
like the epitome of lazy ass products.
I'm just going to stimulate my abs
instead of going to the gym.
No way this is $39. A cyberpunk LED mask
Oh, this has to be like cheaply made.
Like you have to plug it into a wall
when you wear it.
That's sick. It is cool.
It's a full cyberpunk mask. I don't know
if you're able to see out of it, though.
Absolutely badass great quality well put
together craft and the chip is fantastic
killer price and lightning fast
shipping. Carefully packaged can't say
enough hats off.
Delivered quicker quality is great. Only
thing I don't like is a is the
propellers being used as details having
some text saying don't fly this drone
someplace.
What?
Oh, the
Okay, it's like it's homemade, so the
wings are made of like drone propellers.
Like right there.
I see what he means.
I thought he was reviewing a drone for a
second. No, that is a cool ass product.
All right, we have 1 2 3 4 5 6 more.
Uh taxidermied
bunny with reindeer
antlers attached to it.
Yeah,
no.
No.
Oh my god, a karaoke microphone
button mode of preferred style
portable and easy to carry colorful
disco lights Does it come with the
microphone? Really great sound and
volume. Must have if you live with
people that can never hear you calling.
The [\h__\h] does that mean?
Carries very huge sound that'll disturb
the neighbors. What is with Temu people
hating their neighbors?
This Aztec death whistle's great. I walk
outside of my patio at 3:00 in the
morning and just start [\h__\h] screaming
into it.
I'll be playing karaoke. I'll be singing
Lady Gaga at 2:00 in the morning to piss
off my neighbors.
Ooh, it makes my butt bigger. Wait.
This gives me a BBL?
How much do you think this is adding to
my ass?
I feel like
I'm fairly flat.
I feel like it's going to give me
like right around there.
Maybe double size. Maybe double size.
That's not yacht, chat.
All right, last three.
Oh, it's like she's spreading her legs
around your face.
One star, no review.
No text. Courtney De Costa, not a fan of
these sunglasses.
Not a fan. They didn't live up to the
hype.
Is he you Okay, who the [\h__\h] suggested
this? A lung detox? Six main
science-backed ingredients?
I would just feel so weird eating eating
Temu supplements.
Uh it says everything that it has. It's
mullein leaf. What this is supposed to
do is like I because I smoke weed, I
would eat this for like a few days and
over the course of like a week or two, I
would just start like coughing up like
black phlegm.
That's what people say. You start like
coughing up like gross mucus
from your lungs. Oh.
Okay, bad way to end. Bad way to end the
[\h__\h] first half of this video.
Oh.
A hairy chest shirt?
Ew.
Has one review.
I don't want to order that. Okay.
Now we do the complex thing of polling
my chat on what the [\h__\h] we order.
I got to send this straw poll in.
You guys didn't vote for the ocarina.
[\h__\h] you.
Or the Okay, bro, the party helmet you
didn't vote for either? Why did you not
vote for the party helmet?
Nah.
You know what? I'm vetoing the [\h__\h]
drone. [\h__\h] this stupid drone. I'll do
uh
No, I'm vetoing the robot dog, bro,
because that's going to be so stupid.
It's going to take programming and I'm
not doing that. I'm vetoing the robot
dog.
Vetoing it. Vetoing it now. That's my
veto.
Okay, so up we're definitively getting
the shirt, alien drinking beer, African
rain frog, the fryer hydrant, weed
blanket, creepy Grinch, foot massage,
not the dr- Oh, wait, no, I am buying
the drone. The cyberpunk mask, the
realistic fish mask,
remote control inflatable shark.
That's so Why did you guys vote for an
item we didn't review? It's sold out.
Chat, you guys are [\h__\h] the
You guys are [\h__\h] idiots sometimes.
Why is one of the top 20 an item that we
didn't You added it. Bro, be- I I It was
on the list, but I didn't review it cuz
it's sold out. Why did you add it? Bro,
because Brady added all the ones that
were on the [\h__\h] Google page. It's
out It's sold out. We're not getting it.
Why do you add it? Why do you [\h__\h]
vote for an item that we didn't review?
The hairline fixer, unicycle, possum
plush, Dubai chocolate, long Glenn shot.
How is that like top 15? We didn't even
[\h__\h] You guys are [\h__\h]
Well, you Why'd you have it there then?
Well, why'd you [\h__\h] vote for it? You
never even saw me review it. Oh my god.
Okay, I have to write Hold up, I'm
writing myself a note of what we have to
buy. Three weeks later. Half of the [\h__\h]
that came in, I needed to put together
and oh my god, was it a pain. Breaking
news, the unicycle is [\h__\h] broken.
I may have broken it. I think it's for
children. I'm going to go grab it real
quick before we review anything.
I broke the unicycle. I sat on it. I
think it has like a 50-lb weight limit.
It's most definitely for children.
Uh Give me Give me 1 second.
This is the unicycle.
Uh surprisingly took me an hour to put
together when there was only like six
things to screw cuz I'm an idiot and I
didn't know there was a left and right
uh wheel.
Uh now, it's really tiny. Are unicycles
supposed to be this small? I don't know.
I've never seen a unicycle in real life
outside of in movies uh and [\h__\h] This
uh with the clamp doesn't work. Uh when
I sat on it to test it, uh number one
hardest thing to balance on in my entire
life. Uh this rod here drove right
through and almost popped the tire.
Uh I could still Should we still try and
sit on it? Yeah, why not? If I uh the
reason that I really uh wanted to test
this one out before
is because I think that I could die
using this. Uh you see, I just can't sit
on it.
It doesn't [\h__\h] like
Holy [\h__\h]
It kind of It kind of works. Let me move
this out of the way.
It doesn't really You're going to die.
Okay, yeah, no, see, THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
NOT USING THE UNICYCLE. I'M GOING TO
[\h__\h] break my head open. That [\h__\h] is
too dangerous.
Uh the only other product that I wanted
to get out of the way is the Temu
flamethrower, which I had to record
because obviously I can't use it inside.
Uh
it's a fire starter. Uh bit of a
letdown. We'll We'll show you the video
here.
This actually kind of sucks.
Yeah, it's from Temu, but I can't even
see it.
Do less.
It was like the flame was so hot, you
couldn't see it. So we ended up actually
trying to burn something with it.
Uh and it works very well, but it's not
a flamethrower. Look.
Like it instantly set shits It sets
stuff on fire. But it's like
kind of letdown. Also, a little
nerve-racking to attach a propane tank
to something that I bought for $9
on a Chinese website.
But [laughter]
it's, you know, I It worked. I It worked
well, actually. I kept it because I feel
like I could reuse it in at a later
date. Now let's lock in for the actual
review.
>> [snorts]
>> We ordered Dubai chocolate
on Temu. Now,
comes in a clean packaging here.
Uh also, what the [\h__\h] is Dubai
chocolate? Y'all ever eaten it? I feel
like I see a lot of ASMR TikTokers
eat Dubai chocolate a lot. Uh and I'm
pretty sure it's Isn't it just like
pistachio crust on the inside? They like
layer. You do like a chocolate mold.
Okay.
It's melted.
Great. So let's cut this open. It's
slightly
formed weird. Kind of looks gross. That
looks like paint.
Is Should I eat this? Where did this
come from?
It smells like chocolate.
Oh, should we do a cross-section how
they always do?
Looks a little Looks a little a lot
darker
than most Dubai chocolate does.
>> [laughter]
>> I got to eat it. It's getting all over
me.
ASMR?
It's actually really good.
>> [laughter]
[snorts]
>> Oh my god.
No.
It You know what it is? I'm throwing it
out cuz I'm not
I'm not going to eat the rest of that.
It's good though. Have you ever had like
a frozen cat?
Any frozen candy that has the wafers in?
Like it's that crunchy.
I guess that's the appeal of the
texture.
I don't taste the pistachio at all.
It's mainly just the Kit Kat texture
with like a chocolate taste.
What do we think this is?
>> [snorts]
>> I know what it is.
It was uh a little mystery bit here. I
know what's in it. I had to open all of
them because some of them required
Oh, there's chocolate all over my
[\h__\h] hands still. Oh, that's great.
Uh now, I would warn you guys to
potentially
turn down your headsets.
Cuz this is an Aztec death whistle. Uh I
hope this isn't break my mic when I use
this.
Uh I believe you just blow into the top.
I don't know what these notches are for.
Hold up.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
Tell me if I'm using this right.
Everybody
I'd settle down here.
Is that loud for you guys? Because
that's like it actually sounds like
somebody's like a woman screaming in the
middle of the night.
No? I don't know how the mic picks it
up, but it sounds like like a WOMAN'S
GETTING MURDERED.
>> [screaming]
>> WAIT.
IT IS LOUD AND SCARY. COOL PRODUCT. I
will actually keep this. And look, they
give it I you know, every every Temu
product that came here
gave me like a bag.
What the [\h__\h] am I going to use this
for?
I need a carrying bag for my Aztec death
whistle?
We're going to have to turn off the
lights for this. This is this like
What I don't know what was this called?
It's not I don't think I think I don't
think it's like a movie mask. I think
it's just like its own futuristic
Is it the right way? Oh, it's like this.
I have it upside down. This was actually
I'm not Okay, I got to say these things
on the back it's literally just plastic
tubing. Low quality. It is very
innovative. These things here are like
the rotor blades of a [\h__\h] drone.
Like this is just like homemade almost,
which is pretty cool. Let me turn off
the lights real quick. Comes with a It
comes with a shiesty. a ski mask a sha I
don't know what this is called. All
right.
Is it cool?
I don't know. Is it
It's [laughter] No, it's not. Yeah,
balaclava is what it comes with. Okay, I
got to say this is not on par with the
um Iron Man mask. The Iron Man mask
while very faulty was very cool, but
this was also like $30 and Iron Man mask
was like 500. I can't really breathe
very well. Also, these are really
[\h__\h] annoying to look at and they
don't have like a solid set. Oh, they
do. Oh, wow. Yeah, that's really
annoying to look at.
Oh, that's so much better.
Okay, that's good.
That looks pretty good. I think it's
cool. Like what are we rating this at?
It's like for 30 for it was I think it
was like 30 or $40. I'd [\h__\h] rate
that like a nine for the price. But and
it comes with batteries and [\h__\h] too.
And you just got to charge these. Which
is pretty cool. But I mean, I don't know
what type of fit you're going to use
with this. These are annoying as [\h__\h]
That's the one thing I got to say.
Is those Oh, Jesus.
Next.
A beer hat.
Uh it doesn't fit, which is
Do I just have a big head? This can't be
meant for kids, right? Because aren't
these isn't this supposed to be for
beer?
Or is it soda? I remember I had one that
I got from I feel like every guy had one
of these.
Am I wrong? Five Below like 2010. You
could put soda in it, yeah. But it's
like it doesn't fit my head.
Like the hat
the hat like the
There's no way this is just the fact
that I have a large head. I've never had
a problem wearing hats. I don't know.
This also surprisingly took me 10
minutes to figure out how to [\h__\h]
attach these things.
And I got a
I got two Bud Lights.
Now, I didn't clean out the tubes prior.
Do we think that's a safety concern
of sorts?
I don't know if there's like lead or
microplastics that are still sitting in
these. I haven't used one of these since
I was a wee lad. I got to put this
through. Does this go around the front
or the back? Where does this go?
Be careful now.
This could fall at any moment. Do I have
it right? This looks This looks wrong.
It's supposed to be around the front.
Oh, no.
How do you [\h__\h] kink it? How do you
[\h__\h] kink it? How do you [\h__\h] kink
it? It's coming out It's coming out of
the [\h__\h] It's dripping out of the
slot. It's not
It's not stopping. It's not stopping.
It's dripping everywhere. Oh, Jesus.
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
[snorts]
>> WHAT DO I DO? [screaming]
BROTHER. HOLY [\h__\h]
I got to [\h__\h] Hold on.
Oh my god, I got to dump it out. Throw
that to the side. What the [\h__\h] Now my
whole table is covered in [\h__\h] Bud
Light. This towel's soaking wet. Thank
[\h__\h] I grabbed it.
That thing's cool. Only downside is if
you ever want to stop drinking it, you
have to [\h__\h] hold it the whole time.
Because the second you let go, it's just
going to unkink and start flying out of
it. And now my table's sticky. Next. A
possum.
It's a plushy possum.
And it was $95.
This was actually a very expensive Temu
product.
I don't know if it uses real hair or
something. It's very soft.
He looks very happy. I hate to be that
guy. Possums aren't this cute. They're a
lot more
ruggish to say the least. I think
they're
They tend TO BE I HAVE A CUT AND THE
BEER just got in it and it's burning.
Fun fact about possums. They're the only
marsupial in the North in North America,
I think.
Editor, fact check me. Chat, fact check
me. Anyways, this was very expensive. I
don't know what I'm going to do with it.
He has the little loopy tail, too. What
do I do with this? I know people wanted
me to get this because of the dead
possum meme
where I always say I would throw a dead
possum into a nightclub. See how people
react. He has like stars for feet.
Look at him. He's just a little guy.
I could throw this into middle in the
middle of a club. But somebody would
steal him. And then I'd be down $95.
Whereas a dead possum's free on the side
of the road.
You ever see when they carry their kids,
though? That's cute. When a possum
carries their young and they sit on
their back
like that. Oh my god.
Okay, no, they still kind of look
creepy.
It's like
Am I wrong in saying you can't tell if
they look weird or not? Like It's It's
like aw, but
Fun little plushy. Not much to say about
it.
Next.
I don't know what this is. Cuz I didn't
open things
things that were in bags that clearly
didn't need assembly.
Oh.
Like this is just a patch of hair right
here.
Like you know how
You know how sweaty this would be?
Any Like you're in a suit and it's just
rubbing. Like you probably If you got
this much hair on your chest, you
probably got to like baby powder up, no?
If you don't baby powder up, you're
probably going to be like chafing like a
[\h__\h] Just the hair rubbing.
Do we like it, though? The nipples are
very far apart.
My nipples are here.
Their nipples are here.
Might be a big man. Big man here. He's
got wide nipples.
Good distance between them.
Temu smelling salts.
This
uh
It looks very old.
It came like this.
Uh I don't know if it was repackaged
and sold to me. Uh the It says instant
focus effects. 50 g long-lasting
reusable.
The purpose of smelling salts is to
boost arousal in your respiratory I
don't know if I would use that word.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know if I would use that word.
Boost arousal in your respiratory
uh which causes the muscles that control
breathing to be fast-acting and put you
into a fight or flight state. Yeah, it's
cuz your brain thinks you're dying when
you smell ammonia.
So, I'm going to convince my brain that
I'm dying.
>> [laughter]
>> Who's excited?
[cough]
>> They're actually kind of weak.
I I don't want to say these are Temu
smelling salts, but these are Temu. I've
Who Who here has smelled I'm Sorry, I'm
kind of losing consciousness here for a
minute. Who here has smelled smelling
salts before? They wake you up. It
basically feels like you're smelling
fire. It burn No. It It Imagine Like
have you ever gone into like a janitor's
closet? It's like that Oh, it has a
little open cap thing that's still
closed. You're supposed to shake it it
increases the aroma.
Dude, these suck. I like I For me to
smell it burns. But for me to smell it,
I need to be like right next to it. Like
I'm rating that a four, dude. That was a
letdown.
Is this
>> Is this a baby Grinch?
Why did you guys want me to order this?
Genuine question here.
Mini Bart. You think this is a mini-me?
It's green and covered in hair.
Look at it I do have hairy feet. And we
have a foot massage thing so you'll see
that later. But anyways,
this is useless. This is more useless
than the possum. The possum I could have
as some sort of pillow ask plushy. What
the [\h__\h] am I going to do with this?
I could put him in the back when we
change You know when we change our lava
lamp to the Christmas tree
like during December, I could do that.
Well, he'll be a holiday decoration.
He'll make an appearance in a few
months. That's what it'll be.
He'll sit in the back of stream. I don't
want to put him next to the lava lamp
though. I think he'll catch on fire.
This one
uh kind of worries me. I did set this
one up. I used it for probably a
fraction of a second and then turned it
off.
Uh it is
like a zapper machine. How do I describe
this? What is this called chat?
It's the thing that shoots plasma.
And you plug it a Tesla coil. Yeah, this
is a Tesla coil. Uh I never touched it
and I'm saying this right now I'm not
going to touch it.
I think it will electrocute the [\h__\h] out
of me. Uh maybe it'll burn a little. I
don't know. I don't really want to find
out. We got to plug it in though and
turn it on.
So this will be interesting. People
touch it all the time. Well, they give
you two light bulbs with it to try and
see I can't [\h__\h]
Now you turn these knobs. I got to flip
this switch and it'll turn on. Should I
turn off the lights?
Why do I hear it?
Why did Did you guys Am I crazy? I heard
it in my headset before it even started.
Like I heard it. Why? Is it like
interfering?
[\h__\h]
Oh my god. I KNOW THAT I I
THAT SCARES THE [\h__\h] OUT OF ME. I DON'T
WANT TO [\h__\h] keep that on. No, I
DON'T KNOW
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S DUDE, IT'S LITERALLY A [\h__\h]
ELECTRIC SHOCK coming out of the [\h__\h]
stick dude. Am I supposed Is that all Is
that safe? Holy [\h__\h] TOUCH IT? NO. IS
THAT SAFE? Somebody I'm Googling that.
It's generally not recommended to touch
an electric an electric Tesla coil
especially not while it's operating.
Why it's dangerous. They produce high
voltage and up to hundreds of thousands
of volts. Okay, there's not It's not not
this one though.
The current could flow through your body
and cause injury or death. ON THAT?
NO, THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT A big one,
right? Not this [\h__\h] This is like a $40
Tesla coil. They're talking about the
big ones where they got to wear like
chainmail.
Can I touch a toy Tesla coil? It's not
recommended due to electric shock and
burns. I think I'm not going to touch
this.
I think I'll turn it on more. I don't
know what these knobs do. This one makes
it zap quicker. I don't know what this
one does. I'm going to turn this one.
Quiet on set?
Nothing's happening.
IS IT BROKEN?
GET THE [\h__\h] OUT OF HERE. You want me to
touch that [\h__\h] Do you hear it? I'm not
touching that. I'm unplugging that [\h__\h]
IT'S GOING
NO. YOU'RE GOING TO I'M GOING TO GO
YOU'RE OVERREACTING. YEAH, I'm
overreacting. Why don't you [\h__\h]
touch the Tesla coil you [\h__\h] This
is why men die at a younger age because
you're in situations like this WHERE
PEOPLE GO, "HEY, JUST TOUCH THE TESLA
COIL." HEY. HEY JOE, JUST TOUCH THE
TESLA COIL. OH, WHAT'S THE WORST GOING
TO HAPPEN? It electrocutes you because
you're [\h__\h] touching something that's
a middle emitting emitting electricity
out of a wall socket? It is basically a
game where you play hot potato. You see
these little metal things? You put a
bunch of batteries in here and you put
the key in and periodically it'll just
zap the [\h__\h] out of someone. Uh and
you're just supposed to play hot potato
with it. So I'm going to be an absolute
menace and I'm just going to [\h__\h] I'm
going to hold it.
Okay. I think it's on now. So I hold it
and at some point it's going to shock
me.
>> [laughter]
>> I I PUT IT DOWN HE PUT IT DOWN. IT HURT.
IT HURT. IT HURT. It started shock It
started shocking red. Oh my god. Holy
[\h__\h] Okay, hold up. Hold up. Turn it
off. Turn it off. Turn it off. No
reaction.
You'll see You'll know when it shocked
me because of it it turning red and I'm
not going to react.
Okay. Now chat, if you had to guess, do
you think it's shocked me yet?
Do you No. Yeah, see it hasn't yet.
I'm still waiting.
I think it might be off.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
I'm done. It's not like getting tased.
I've gotten I I've never gotten tased
with like a like a [\h__\h] gun taser,
but I gotten tased once in the arm by
like a hand taser. It's not nearly as
painful as that. This is a toy, but it's
like not like this. Did y'all ever have
the game where there were four metal
prongs? It would be some [\h__\h] you'd get
from Five Below. It'd be four metal
prongs and you and like three of your
friends would hold on to one and it
would do like a like roulette and it
would go donk donk donk donk donk donk
donk donk and then it would zap the [\h__\h]
out of someone. And on level five or
like the highest level you'd be like,
"Ah [\h__\h] that hurts." It's probably
like a four but four out of five on the
toy scale. Out of pain it's like a
three. It's more so just like like
shocking that it happens. It's cool
though.
Waste of money. Whoever the [\h__\h]
suggested this, what the hell am I going
to do with this? It's a miniature
What is this called? Fire hydrant.
About no use for it. Lick it? Why?
Pee on it? No.
>> [laughter]
>> I think this is a piece of [\h__\h] product.
This was also like $30 and they promoted
it using AI. Like editor flashback to
the image. They would just like take a
picture of this and then like AI input
it at a park. Like I guess it could be a
useful decoration, but who the [\h__\h]
would want to use this to decorate? It
has I think it's for outside cuz it has
these little notches so you can nail it
into the ground. When Who the [\h__\h] would
put this outside as as as a decorative
piece? I've never been attracted to the
look of a fire hydrant. It's a [\h__\h]
fire hydrant. I have not opened this.
What do we think it is? For the people
that remember what we ordered.
It's a sword. It's a sword. I'll spoil
it. Now it is sheathed I'm noticing.
I think this Was this the most expensive
thing we ordered chat? It probably
weighs like 30 lb with the sheath.
Ooh.
It's not sharp at all. The tip is.
I bet it would still cut something if
you hacked into someone, but it's not
sharp. It's like a dull blade which is
still cool. I think it's more of like a
showpiece than actually something you
would use, but I mean dude, come on.
That is
badass. That's like a 3-ft blade.
Is this a double-hander? This would be a
dual wielder. Look how perfect that sits
too.
That is [\h__\h] badass with the sheath
as well.
Where do I hit him?
I'm thinking right here.
Or right here.
I'm sorry Bob.
It's dead doll.
The only thing that happened is some of
the paint rubbed off on him.
It goes through. It goes through.
On the stab.
I feel like I'm a part of a Do you
remember
or not not not American Ninja Warrior?
What was that show where they went
through like older classes of like army
men and they would see which one was
more able to kill people?
No, not Forged in Fire. I think it was
something Deadliest Warrior. Was it just
Deadliest Warrior? I think that was the
name of the show. Right about here. I'm
going to give this a three out of 10
kill counter. I think it's kind of a
weak blade, no slashing potential. Uh
stabbing somewhat, but even then I think
it's more of a showpiece sword uh as
it's dull than anything. I think this is
something that you're supposed to hang
up not actually use. 10 out of 10 though
blast. Bob did a great job. Everybody
thank you, Bob. Thank you, Bob. You ate
one for the team.
You ate one for the team. Thank you.
It came in like this. I need to know I
need you guys to know came in like this.
I didn't crumple the box. It came in
like this. It's a big toothbrush. Uh
also I must say little false marketing
here. There's a little false marketing
here. I thought this was going to be the
world's biggest toothbrush. They say uh
it's a bath brush bath brush jumbo. Bath
brush jumbo. Isn't this a little small?
When I watched the ads for it, it looked
about yay big. And the brush would what
I thought the brush would be as big as
the whole handle. This thing is ass. Now
it does it is very it is a very simple
comfy loofah feel.
Kind of works as a back scratcher as
well.
I just fear the bristles condition after
washing the
butt region.
I think this would get pretty gross
pretty fast. I think after a few a few a
few goes in the shower, I think this
would be mhm
brown not white.
Lightsabers.
Lightsabers Temu lightsabers $40. I
think pretty cool product. Haven't used
it yet. I had to charge them and I made
sure they turned on and now we're going
to put them together. Now this one the
cool thing about these Temu products, if
I could [\h__\h] get them out. The cool
thing about this is they have an
interconnective bit right here.
Uh so you can actually use them as if
they were
um
what's it called? What is that called,
chat? You know what I'm talking about.
Like you're a dude from Star Wars. I'm
using the wrong that's the wrong end.
This is the right end. Is this the right
end? This is the right end.
How do I change color? Wait, that's not
the same color. There it is.
Now you probably can't hear it but they
do make the wom wom.
I'll I'll input that myself. Wom.
Wom wom.
How do you use a a a lightsaber? Don't
you just go like this? Wom wom wom wom
wom wom wom wom. You ever see the videos
where like people that are really into
Star Wars join like clubs and they have
to get like anointed into the Star Wars?
You are now a Jedi. Welcome to the
order. Doesn't really make sense cuz
that would singe your skin off.
I'm not trying to be hypercritical, but
if we're really getting into character
here, if I anointed you into the Star
Wars Jedi
legion, this would you it would BE LIKE
I NOW ANOINT
>> [screaming]
>> ANOINT YOU TO
AND BOTH OF YOUR ARMS WOULD JUST GET
[\h__\h] sliced off. Anyways, great
product. I enjoyed that.
Now has a [\h__\h] sticker on it on a
fluffy blanket that you actually just
can't get off.
Does this have to stay on the product?
I can't get it off. All right, whatever.
All right, well
it's a weed blanket.
Put some alcohol on that [\h__\h] I'd
probably just have to throw it in the
wash and I assume it would come out. It
kind of smells like
you ever go into like an antique store
and you're like oh has my grandma been
here?
Ah no, just smells like mothballs. It
smells like uh you ever go into an old
person home and it got it kind of has
that stench of like lemonade but pee.
Like that's the vibe that this blanket
gives smelling wise.
Mixed with a bit of cleaning supplies. I
I'm not a fan of it. I think it's a very
thin cheap blanket, but you know, it was
a custom weed blanket that they printed.
It's pretty cool. I'll use it on stream
in the winter when I'm chilly. I'm not
going to throw it out, but
next. First one
tasty sounds. This is one of those
lollipops very similar to a
um toothbrush. If you remember Tooth
Tunes, I think it was called. This is a
lollipop
that has preloaded on it. So when you're
eating it, I think it's supposed to
vibrate a song in your mouth or maybe
play it out of a speaker. I don't really
know. Tooth Tunes, it's a lollipop.
It smells like blue like a blueberry
Jolly Rancher and apparently it's
supposed to play tunes.
Can you guys hear it?
Wow.
>> [snorts]
>> This is the best product ever made.
I hear it. Like it vibrates in my teeth
and I hear it in my brain.
It's going uh
uh
Bro, [laughter] I'm I swear to god I'm
not tweaking. SHE'S GOING
UH
>> [laughter]
>> I'M NOT INSANE. BRO, IT WORKS. OKAY,
THIS is not like Tooth Tunes. This is
not like Tooth Tune or or whatever the
[\h__\h] toothbrush one was cuz the
toothbrush one would play music. This
actually vibrates
like in my mouth. I think I turned it
off. It only has one song though.
It's like a 10-second loop and it it'll
go uh uh uh uh uh uh
uh
and then it'll go back and that's all I
hear.
I'm sorry for the VOD viewers. We're
going to have to cut that [\h__\h] out.
That's probably copyrighted. This one's
strawberry flavor. I'LL KEEP IT. NEXT.
CAN YOU READ THAT?
It is scalp care hair growth spray.
Reactivates hair follicles to stimulate
and reduces hair loss. Unscented 1-month
supply. Use twice daily for effects. Uh
it has metha hapocalex oil. You know,
I'm kind of I know you guys sent this to
me as a meme because you're saying I'm
balding. Uh and I do kind of worry about
having receding hairline not really hair
thinning, but I kind of worry that the
Temu hairspray might trigger my baldness
versus fix it.
Unscented in my ass. It smells like
[\h__\h] Febreze. It smells like [\h__\h]
It smells like [\h__\h] like pumpkin
spice Febreze. The hell is this?
>> [cough]
>> Next one you guys made me order was a
lung cleanse.
So now we're just getting medical
products from Temu uh which is you know
somewhat interesting I guess. Uh it just
has a bunch of vitamin zinc mullein
leaf. Uh I think the I get a lot of
TikTok ads for lung cleansing products
from fake doctors. Uh specifically this
one old middle-aged man who wears
medical scrubs uh and goes You've been
smoking a lot, haven't you? You need to
get this mullein leaf all right now on
the TikTok shop. Buddy, if you're a
doctor, you ain't need to be promoting
some TikTok shop ass product for [\h__\h]
5% affiliate money, buddy. I know your
ass ain't a [\h__\h] doctor. You're
wearing doctor scrubs sitting in an
office [\h__\h] prescribing me medicine.
You're not a doctor. I don't even know
if you went to college.
Am I am I going to take the Temu pills?
How what's the
Okay, serving size is two capsules. It
just has a bunch of leaf blends. Lung
healthy and cleanse respiratory health
immune health. All-in-one supplement.
Mullein leaf lung respiratory aid immune
60 capsules. Do not exceed the
recommended dose pregnant nursing women
children under the 18 and individuals
with pre-existing medical conditions
should consult a physician before
thinking about taking this. As a dietary
supplement take two a day in parentheses
these statements have not been evaluated
by the FDA. This product is not intended
to diagnose treat cure or prevent any
disease. Oh, that's great. Two pills,
eh?
OH, TEMU PILLS. HERE we go. Mullen leaf
down the hatch.
OH! OH, JOE, DON'T TAKE THE TEMU PILLS,
but when it comes to touching a [\h__\h]
electric zapper, that we're drawing the
line at Mullen leaf Temu, but we're not
drawing the line but we're not drawing
the line at me [\h__\h] electrocuting
myself.
Temu drone.
I tried flying it cuz I had to make sure
it worked.
Not a great pilot.
The controls
are a lot more complicated than it
seems. There's about what? 2 4 6 8 nine
buttons on the front and then four on
the sides.
So, this is going to be interesting.
Now, I will say when I check when I
tested this out, I crashed it three
times.
Which is already off to a better start
than any of those toy You remember Toys
"R" Us helicopters and you would get
them when you were a kid? Already better
than those because those were taking a
piece of [\h__\h]
to the next level. Like I mean, they you
would crash them one time, they'd break.
I'm going to zoom the camera out so you
could see it slightly.
Let's see if we can fly it. I don't
remember the controls and I'm too lazy
to look.
Bring it back. Bring it back.
[\h__\h]
>> [screaming]
>> AND LAND THAT [\h__\h] AND LAND THAT
[\h__\h]
BRINGING IT DOWN EASY. ROGER.
OH, [\h__\h]
I'm a goated for that. Okay. Should we
try and land it on something?
What should I try and land it on? The
lava lamp? Okay, fine.
Hello?
It might be broken.
I did crash it. It's not fine.
I think it's broken.
Why is it Why is it ticking like it's
going to explode?
Lock in.
GOING FOR THE LANDING. I REPEAT.
Going for the landing. Taking it in
Taking it in nice and slow.
Nice and slow on top of the lava lamp.
Let's get it a little forward.
A little left.
Get ready to bring it down.
Bringing it down.
Micro movements.
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
MINI FROG.
Temu frog. He's a little sad guy. I
think we got a cool one. When we were
looking at them when we ordered them,
they all looked different and I honestly
think this one's kind of higher quality.
He's a little grumpy, but he's a cool
handmade frog. He looks like the top of
it's going to give me warts.
I've had warts before as well on my
feet. I used to scrape them on the
asphalt because I remember I wanted to
get rid of them and then they went away
and I haven't had them in years.
This is the ab machine. If you don't
remember me ordering this, it's supposed
to give me a six pack. It has like three
electric prongs similar to the electric
thing that we had previously, but that
was just a muscle simulator. This one's
specifically made for your abs. So,
we're going to use this and see if I
feel as if I'm having an ab workout. I
also think this is the one people use
when they're testing to see if they're
like pregnant. It only It only has two
of these notches here. So, I think the
third one's if I wanted to use it on
like my legs cuz they have a leg
attachment as well, but we've already
done that, so we're just going to use
the chest one. Oh, wait, no. It only has
one for the chest region.
That's kind of ass, no? Do you think
it'll be strong enough? What are these
for? What do you think these are for? My
side region?
Let me look at this woman here.
Your back, your chest.
If you're actually trying to get in
shape, maybe working out is the answer
and eating better, not ordering a Temu
electric stimulator.
That was a motivational message here.
This isn't really working out. This is
me attaching a product to my stomach
that's going to force my abs to flex.
Oh, it's [\h__\h] sticky, dude. This [\h__\h]
is going to This not This is not going
to come off.
Let's get a zoom going here.
Uh it feels like you're punching me in
the stomach like this.
It's not it Actually, I kind of like it.
It's like It's almost painful
but in a good way.
>> [laughter]
>> It kind of hurts.
Is this safe? I I don't
Oh
my god, that's 10. How high do you think
it goes? Should we go higher?
[\h__\h] THAT HURTS.
OH MY GOD.
OW.
OW. OH.
OH, WHAT THE [\h__\h] I JUST CHANGED THE
MODE. OH MY GOD. OH MY GOD. OH MY GOD.
Oh my god, no.
It was doing a doom doom doom doom and
[clears throat] now it's just going
It's like making my abs
>> [sighs]
>> Ah.
>> [snorts]
>> AH.
>> [screaming]
OH MY GOD, THAT'S ONLY LEVEL THREE. HOLY
[\h__\h] THAT HURTS.
AH.
GOD DAMN IT.
OW.
OW. OW. OW. OW, turn it off. Turn it
off. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it
off.
Holy [\h__\h]
Holy [\h__\h] That second one was
unenjoyable.
Now, do my abs look more defined?
I don't think at all. I think they look
the same.
Next product here. It's the fish mask.
Smells like Sharpies and boy do I love
the smell of Sharpies. What's
I think this is the mouth hole. I'm I
can see through this if I go like that.
I don't know if you can hear me, but the
eye holes are right here and they're not
You can't [\h__\h] see anything.
Maybe I am supposed to see through that.
I mean, dude, this is like a [\h__\h]
fever dream. This is like a trip
nightmare. I feel like I have I have
straight up tunnel vision. I can see you
through this.
Like I I only see my chat right now. It
looks amazing. What is the [\h__\h]
practical usage in this? Who's wearing
this [\h__\h] fish mask? When I [\h__\h]
bought it, it had a bunch of images of
people wearing it and I'm like they were
on a plane. One of them was on a plane.
I'm like you're just bringing this on an
air You're You're on an airplane wearing
a [\h__\h] fish mask. What are you using
this for? I think this is the alien.
Oh, don't tell me his beer mug broke. He
was just the chill the chill alien with
the beer. I think I could put it in his
hand. Oh, he can hold it. Okay.
Look at him.
And he's going
right on the edge right on the edge of
the fridge.
Just hitting me with a
gnarly pose.
The problem is I think he's going to
fall off whenever the fridge turns on
cuz when the fridge turns on, all the
Funko pops on top shake and I think
he'll fall off.
It's a foot massage machine.
You know, I'm not trying to be too nosy
of a person right now, but why would you
ever want this? I've never a foot cam.
Oh, yeah, we're going to get a foot cam
going on here.
I mean Chad, it's not going to be a
[\h__\h] review if I don't have a foot
cam. Should I put socks on?
Not a very long range on the cord.
Oh, yeah. Oh, that's going to be nice.
Is that heat or cool? What do we think
that is?
It's got these little balls that jiggle.
Oh, and you can change direction as
well.
Yeah, it'll apply some heat. Okay, let's
move the table.
Activating foot massage.
I'll shine a flashlight on them.
Is there a better mode?
No lie, this kind of sucks.
It's like this the weakest mode of a of
a mall massager. It's just like tickling
my feet. I want I want the feeling that
a bulky man named Brutus is is gripping
up my toes. And right now, I'm getting
the feeling that, you know, somebody's
like touching them with a bristle. Like
that's all it is.
It's not really doing much for me. It's
actually doing like nothing for me. How
do I make it stronger?
It doesn't get stronger. Oh wait, no,
that does. Oh my god, it does. That's
the mode. Oh, yeah. No, that's good.
You see the micro movements there? It's
really getting my bunion.
Under my first metatarsal. Wow. Okay.
>> [snorts]
>> Oh, it's Oh my god, it just stopped and
now it's doing the reverse. Ooh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh my god.
Right where it's sore on the [\h__\h]
arch. Yeah.
Okay. I'm scared, brother.
You're just watching me get a foot
massage.
When you think about it, when you think
about it, why are you watching me get a
foot massage right now? Isn't that
I don't know. I mean
Is an ocarina.
Now, I don't know how to use this.
I played the flute in elementary school,
but the flute was a lot simpler
than an ocarina.
It It comes with a little hand holder,
and I don't know how you're supposed to
What the [\h__\h] is this?
What is this for?
The [\h__\h] hand.
It's a Zelda reference?
I'm not going to drop it. What do you
blow into? There's like 50 holes.
That's not a hole.
Do I blow into the bottom?
Flip it.
What's up, Ocarina amigos? My name is
David, and this is the first video
Ocarina amigos. Ocarina amigos, I love
this guy. you in a 12-lesson series
titled How to Play Ocarina. This video
series works right alongside of my new
book of the same name, How to Play
Ocarina, which is available at
daviderikramos.com/store.
It's
All right, all right, all right. Let's
get to the overview, buddy. special
arrangements to play with your friend
from. In the last couple years, there
have been a flood of these new Zelda
ocarinas THAT ARE REALLY
>> [screaming]
>> THAT DOES NOT HOLD IT. THAT IS NOT
[\h__\h]
Am I doing this right? music experience
to make sure that it's in tune. And even
if it's not in tune, you can still USE
THE PART ONE OF 14?
NAH. YO, it's cooked. It's cooked, Eric
Ramos.
All right, what song did I just play?
Uh it was uh Thriller by Michael
Jackson.
Next one.
All right, how about now?
Johann Sebastian Bach's fifth symphony.
Next.
Fetty [snorts] Wap.
What song? I'll play it one more time.
Oh my god, wait, that sounded beautiful.
Wait.
Trap Queen. Okay, next.
Butt pants. Now, should I put my actual
pants over these? Or do I wear them like
this?
Hold on, let me pose.
I could hit a mean twerk on these right
now. Hold up.
>> [snorts]
>> Editor, play some good non-copyrighted
twerk music.
>> [music]
[music]
>> ABOUT TO HIT THAT ONE-LEG TWERK.
>> [music]
>> These are actually pretty comfortable, I
got to say. It's like a cushion. I might
wear these next time I go on a plane.
You know, when your butt starts hurting
cuz the plane seat's unbearable? This
[\h__\h]
It's like its own butt cushion. It's
nice.
The final product of the Temu review
is
a dusty
smoker's pipe.
It looks used.
Doesn't smell used, but it looks old. I
am willing to try and use weed in it and
see if it works.
Out of curiosity.
Uh now, I don't plan on getting really
high this stream, but I would take a
ripskies to test the product. Editor's
going to have to [\h__\h] blur the [\h__\h]
out of all of this.
>> [laughter]
>> What the hell is this? How can you sit
here and Let me
Let me think about that.
No, let me go grab weed real quick.
Play a sad song.
How the [\h__\h] AM I SUPPOSED TO LIGHT IT?
HOW DO I LIGHT HOW DO I LIGHT IT WITHOUT
BURNING the [\h__\h] on my hand? I need to
get like a stick lighter. Holy [\h__\h]
Now, we're just sawing. W [\h__\h] Temu
review. I really enjoyed it. I thought
it was fun. I hope you guys thought it
was fun. I think we had some good
products.
We'll definitely run it back. Probably
next time we might do another Temu
review one.
Temu, hit me up. We might be doing like
a more expensive one. Get to get a lot
of products. Like a [\h__\h] full 4-hour
review. But we'll definitely run it
back. We might do TikTok Shop again
soon, which is really cool.
So, we'll do that, but what's happening
with the reacts?